Hubungi

www.linkedin.com/in/arbidwiwijaya (LinkedIn)

Keahlian Teratas

React.js

Bootstrap

Mocha (JavaScript Framework)

Certifications

Full-Stack JavaScript Developer
Full-Stack Golang & Vue JS:
CrowdFunding Website
Fullstack Website Developer
MERN Stack Web Development
2021

Arbi Dwi Wijaya

Frontend Web Developer | ReactJS Malang

Ringkasan

Hello... My full name is Arbi Dwi Wijaya, so you can call me "ARBI". I'm Software Engineer Web who specialized in FRONTEND side. Very passionate about modern web technology using JavaScript/ TypeScript while taking into consideration the latest trends and techniques.

Pengalaman

STIKI Malang Frontend Web Developer April 2019 - Agustus 2019 (5 bulan) Malang, Jawa Timur, Indonesia

Membuat Sisten UKM untuk kampus STIKI Malang.

Mengkonversi mockups menjadi aplikasi berbasis web. Dalam pembuatan Aplikasi ini saya menggunakan framework Bootstrap.

Dinas Komunikasi dan Informatika Programmer Mei 2014 - Agustus 2014 (4 bulan) Surabaya, Jawa Timur, Indonesia

Pendidikan

Arkademy

Talent, Full stack Web Developer · (2020 - 2021)

STIKI Malang

Teknik Informatika · (2015 - 2021)

SMK Nasional Malang

Rekayasa Perangkat Lunak · (2012 - 2015)